freeppt.net 2015-08-16

# Free PPT, Powerpoint Templates, Backgrounds and Powerpoint 2013 Templates

## Privacy Policy 

We take our customers' privacy very seriously, and go to great lengths to protect any details you provide to us.

FreePPT.net Office's Customer Privacy Policy explains why we collect information about our customers, what information is collected when you interact with FreePPT.net—by visiting our website, purchasing our products/services or by contacting our customer inquiries— and how that information will be used. We believe your your privacy is our priority, and we will do our best to protect it and respect it. Please take a moment to read over our privacy policy and learn more about our data practices.

**

#### Why do we collect personal information?

**

We collect information about our customers in order to provide higher levels of customer service for our users and to properly deliver our software licenses. By collecting information, we are able to let you know about products and services that may interest you, and as well as keep you updated with about new releases, special offers, product updates and upcoming events.

**

#### What information will we collect from you and how will it be used?

**

Information collected from FreePPT.net Office customers includes: names, mailing addresses, email addresses, contact preferences, credit/debit card information and the details of the FreePPT.net products owned by the customer, such as: FreePPT.net Office serial number, date of purchase and any previous customer service issues. This information is used for a number of purposes:

• When responding to customer inquiries - having background information about our customers helps our staff assist you more efficiently.

• In situations involving downloading software updates, participating in online surveys, registering for seminars, registering to purchase products, or discussing a service issue, customer account information is necessary.

• For market research- this helps us to understand our customers better, enabling us to improve our products and services by accounting for such things as occupation and computing habits.

• Personal information may be used in order to provide requested products or to conduct audits, analysis and research.

• Website improvement - we collect data on how customers interact with our website.

**

#### When and where do we disclose personal information?

**

At FreePPT.net office we value our relationships with our customers and therefore promise to you that we will never sell or rent your personal information to third party marketers.

Within the FreePPT.net Office organization, personal information may be shared with legal entities in order to establish how to develop superior services for our customers. Measures are taken however, to ensure that this data is handled sensitively, in accordance with FreePPT.net's Customer Privacy Policy.

Externally, FreePPT.net Office has working relationships with companies who provide products and services to our customers on our behalf. It is therefore sometimes necessary to provide these companies with information about our customers so that they can:

•Deliver quality products and services to you

•Complete customer transactions

•Extend customer credit

•Provide high standards of customer service

•Manage and enhance our collection of customer information

•Provide higher levels of customer service

•Assess customers' interest in specific products and services

•Conduct market research and measure customer satisfaction levels

Any Companies that who have access to our customer data are bound by FreePPT.net's Customer Privacy Policy as well to protect your data; in the case of exceptions, you will be notified at the upon collection.

Furthermore, FreePPT.net is duty-bound to release customer information if it is in the interests of national security, enforcement of the law or other issues of public importance. FreePPT.net is also required by law or litigation to disclose private information if it is deemed necessary.

#### How do we protect your private information?

FreePPT.net office takes a number of precautions to ensure that your data cannot be lost, stolen, misused, subjected to unauthorized access, disclosed, changed or destroyed. These measures include: Administrative, Technical,Physical.

When purchasing products or services from us, a secure server is used that is hosted by Paypal, SWREG and other third party payment processors. All of the data, including names, addresses, credit/debit card numbers, expiration dates, etc, is encrypted before being sent to FreePPT.net. Encryption is difficult to decode and prevents your payment details being stolen and misused.

There are also a number of ways that you, the user, can protect yourself from malicious attacks online. Always use a secure web browser and try to change your passwords regularly, ideally mixing numbers and letters together.

**

#### FreePPT.net Office's Policy Regarding Malware

**

FreePPT.net is firmly against all kinds of malware, and it is our promise that no piece of FreePPT.net software will intentionally compromise a user's security or privacy. All FreePPT.net software can be manually uninstalled from devices easily, through a designated uninstall utility. All of FreePPT.net's software has passed vigorous Kaspersky and Rising anti-virus/malware tests before being released to the public. This means that no FreePPT.net software will have features similar to the features of malware; reinstallers are not employed, information that would allow someone to personally identify a user is not collected, and they will not contain any hidden third party applications such as spyware, malware, adware, viruses, worms, Trojan's, etc. Overall, FreePPT.net software will not jeopardize any customer's privacy or security.

**

#### FreePPT.net Office's Commitment to Privacy

**

The FreePPT.net Customer Privacy Policy is communicated to all employees and a number of privacy safeguards are strictly enforced throughout the company in order to protect our users' personal data. This policy is applicable worldwide and covers the Intel Corporate website.

**

#### International Users

**

The FreePPT.net Customer Privacy Policy is under the safe harbour framework established by the US Department of Commerce, concerning the gathering, usage and storing of personal data collected from the EU.

Links to other companies can be found on the FreePPT.net website. FreePPT.net would like to state that we are not responsible or accountable for the privacy policies of those websites although we would actively encourage the individual user to examine those privacy policies before providing personal information about themselves.
